Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Born-Digital Photographs, 1999-2019
  - Unsorted University photographs, 1999-2004
    - Students brush up on a math lesson through the..., 2001
    - Distinguished Professor Judith Langer (director of..., 2001
    - A participant in a Partnership for Literacy..., 2001
    - Professor Gloria Ladson-Billings of the University..., 2001
    - Professor Gloria Ladson-Billings of the University..., 2001
    - Donald Faulkner, Director, New York State Writer's..., 2001
    - Unidentified man participates in discussion with..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2001
    - Kangwon National University President Yong Soo..., 2001
    - Unidentified speakers shake hands at the 25th..., 2001
    - An unidentified woman stands to be recognized at..., 2001
    - Members of the University at Albany's Professional..., 2001
    - An unidentified man speaks at a legislative..., 2001
    - Programs are handed out for a September 11th..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2001
    - An unidentified speaker addresses the crowd after..., 2001
    - An unidentified University at Albany student who..., 2001
    - Sandy Zaleski receiving a Certificate of..., 2002
    - Audience at the New York State Nurses Association..., 2002
    - Unidentified persons in the audience at the New..., 2002
    - Helen Desfosses looks at Eliot Spitzer at the..., 2002
    - Eliot Spitzer addresses the Boosting Business in..., 2002
    - V. Mark Durand, Department of Psychology,..., 2002 March 11
    - An unidentified man and woman attend the..., 2004 March 11
    - Carlos Santiago, officer in charge and provost,..., 2004 March 11
    - An unidentified man speaks with newly appointed..., 2004 March 12
    - Newly appointed University at Albany interim..., 2004 March 12
    - An unidentified man speaks with newly appointed..., 2004 March 12
    - The University at Albany's Initiatives For Women..., 2003 March 17
    - An unidentified person speaks at the podium at a..., 2003 March 19
    - University at Albany Provost Carlos Santiago..., 2003 March 24
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2003 March 24
    - Unidentified high school students tour the..., 2003 March 27
    - Mike Krause, research scientist at Thomson..., 2004 March 3
    - Chad Waxman, Class of 2003, is pursuing a master's..., 2004 March 31
    - Kenneth Jackson (left) and an unidentified person..., 2002 March 4
    - Don Faulkner, director of the New York State..., 2004 March 4
    - Billy Collins, recipient of the New York State..., 2004 March 4
    - Unidentified persons speaking together during the..., 2002 April 1
    - Unidentified persons speaking together during the..., 2002 April 1
    - Unidentified persons working during the Annual..., 2002 April 1
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) Regional..., 2002 April 1
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2002 April 10
    - Albany Mayor Jerry Jennings shakes hands with an..., 2002 April 10
    - Albany Mayor Jerry Jennings shakes hands with..., 2002 April 10
    - University at Albany School of Business Dean..., 2002 April 11
    - Towers Perrin management consultant and University..., 2002 April 11
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 22
    - Antonia Coello Novello, New York State..., 2002 April 22
    - From left, John Ryan, University at Albany interim..., 2004 April 28
    - John Ryan, University at Albany interim president,..., 2004 April 28
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock,..., 2002 April 3
    - New York State Governor George Pataki speaking at..., 2002 April 3
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 3
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 3
    - Alain Kaloyeros, Dean of the School of..., 2002 April 30
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 30
    - The founding members of the University at Albany..., 2002 April 30
    - Tom Brokaw, anchor and managing editor of NBC..., 2002 April 30
    - (Left to right) John Ryan, University at Albany..., 2004 April 30
    - University at Albany Interim President John Ryan..., 2004 April 30
    - U.S. EPA Administrator Christie Whitman during a..., 2002 April 5
    - U.S. EPA Administrator Christie Whitman during a..., 2002 April 5
    - Administrator of the EPA Christine Whitman during..., 2002 April 5
    - Administrator of the EPA Christine Whitman during..., 2002 April 5
    - Judy Genshaft, University at Albany Provost, and..., 1999 April 9
    - Associate Vice President for Academic Affair sat..., 2003 April 9
    - From the left, Susan Palmer, Carson Carr, Jr., and..., 2003 April 9
    - The graduating University at Albany 2004 Masters..., 2004 May 11
    - From left, an unidentified woman, an unidentified..., 2004 May 13
    - University at Albany librarian Carol Ann Germain..., 2004 May 14
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2003 May 15
    - Frank Thompson, Dean of the Rockefeller College of..., 2003 May 15
    - Lynn Gilmore Canton and Frank Thompson, Dean of..., 2003 May 15
    - Individuals attend a pre-commencement dinner for..., 2004 May 15
    - Catherine Bertini prior to attending the 2002 John..., 2002 May 16
    - A display of the awards at the 2002 John E. Burton..., 2002 May 16
    - An unidentified person at the 2002 John E. Burton..., 2002 May 16
    - An unidentified person shakes hands with Catherine..., 2002 May 16
    - Ladan Alomar speaking at the 2002 John E. Burton..., 2002 May 16
    - James Acker (center), University at Albany..., 2002 May 16
    - The 2004 undergraduate departmental graduation..., 2004 May 16
    - Donna Coonley of the Albany City Schools attends..., 2004 May 18
    - Lee McElroy Jr. (left), University at Albany..., 2004 May 3
    - Lee McElroy Jr. (left), University at Albany..., 2004 May 3
    - Abisogun Leigh of Lagos State University presents..., 2004 May 3
    - Abisogun Leigh of Lagos State University and an..., 2004 May 3
    - Abisogun Leigh (right) of Lagos State University..., 2004 May 3
    - An unidentified person speaking at the Great Dane..., 2003 May 5
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 May 5
    - WNYT-NBC 13 Sports Reporter Rodger Wyland speaking..., 2003 May 5
    - Sara Rickard and an unidentified person hold an..., 2003 May 5
    - MVP of Women's Volleyball Alissa Gibbs and Head..., 2003 May 5
    - Head Baseball Coach John Mueller poses with..., 2003 May 5
    - Tamika Bent and Lekeasha Hales, University at..., 2002 May 6
    - University at Albany students particiate in the..., 2004 May 6
    - An unidentified man speaks at an event honoring..., 2004 May 6
    - The University at Albany chorus sings at the..., 2004 May 7
    - Peter Bloniarz, dean of the College of Computing..., 2004 May 7
    - Outgoing University at Albany President Karen..., 2004 May 7
    - (Left to right) outgoing University at Albany..., 2004 May 7
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 May 9
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 May 9
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 May 9
    - Donna Regenstreif at an aging seminar with the..., 2003 June 11
    - Ceramic art "You Are Here" created by M.F.A...., 2003 June 17
    - Frances '71 and David Martin '53 speak with Eunice..., 2002 June 20
    - Harold Hanson '63, Benevolent Association Business..., 2002 June 20
    - Professor Karla Goldman addresses the audience at..., 2002 June 20
    - University of Minnesota Professor of American..., 2002 June 20
    - From left, Alain Kaloyeros, Professor of..., 2004 June 22
    - Chancellor of the State University of New York..., 2003 June 24
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno stands at the..., 2003 June 24
    - Donor Mary Polsinello Hanley, Chancellor of the..., 2003 June 24
    - University at Albany Provost and Vice President of..., 2003 June 24
    - Beatrice Gluckman and Eleanor Korfman pose with an..., 2003 June 3
    - Professor of Judaic Studies Mark Raider,..., 2003 June 3
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 June 3
    - Julia Koschinsky, Director of the Center for Women..., 2003 June 30
    - Margery Saunders, Center for Women in Government &..., 2003 June 30
    - Two unidentified alumnae attend 2004 Alumni..., 2004 June 4
    - Anthony Giardina, Class of 1981, speaks at an..., 2004 June 4
    - From the left: Dr. Lois Rosado, SUNY Brooklyn..., 2002 June 5
    - From the left: Christine Haile, Chief Information..., 2002 June 5
    - Unidentified persons standing together at a..., 2003 June 9
    - Laura Robbins of the Hartford Foundation seated at..., 2003 June 9
    - Dawn DiMicco and Monica Whitney seated at a..., 2003 June 9
    - "Before" pictures of a dorm room in the State Quad..., 2002 July 17
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 July 18
    - President and CEO of SEMATECH North C. Robert..., 2002 July 18
    - Employees of the University at Albany's Public..., 2002 July 23
    - A recent book by University at Albany professor..., 2003 July 24
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock,..., 2003 July 25
    - Head Coach of the Giants Jim Fassel speaks with..., 2003 July 25
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 July 25
    - Albany County Legislator Michael Breslin and..., 2002 July 26
    - University at Albany School of Criminal Justice..., 2003 July 26
    - An unidentified person standing at an event..., 2003 July 29
    - Dennis Sugumele speaks at a check presentation by..., 2004 July 8
    - Unidentified persons from the University at..., 2002 August 13
    - Jason Adriano, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Ritka Ferwani, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Mihir Kaji, member of the class of 2005 masters of..., 2003 August 28
    - Matthew Mead, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Ravi Pherwani, member of the class of 2005 masters..., 2003 August 28
    - Pei Wang, member of the class of 2005 masters of..., 2003 August 28
    - Madeleine Kunin, Diplomat and Politician, gives..., 2003 September 18
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock,..., 2003 September 18
    - Margaret Krause, chair of the board of directors..., 2003 September 18
    - New York State Senator Joseph Bruno speaks at an..., 2002 September 19
    - New York Senator Kemp Hannon stands at the seventh..., 2003 January 14
    - Unidentified persons seated in the audience at the..., 2003 January 14
    - Unidentified person in the Center for..., 2002 January 15
    - Dr. Shahedipour-Sandvik's lab at the University at..., 2003 January 16
    - Unidentified persons at a presentation on Case..., 2002 January 18
    - Unidentified persons at a presentation on Case..., 2002 January 18
    - The University at Albany's pep band rehearses in..., 2004 January 21
    - The University at Albany's pep band rehearses in..., 2004 January 21
    - An unidentified woman protests at an event for..., 2004 January 22
    - Scott Fein, attorney at Whiteman Osterman & Hanna..., 2004 January 22
    - J. Kevin Doolen, chair of the Department of..., 2004 January 27
    - New York State Governor George Pataki seated..., 2003 January 28
    - New York State Governor George Pataki, New York..., 2003 January 28
    - News media interview University at Albany..., 2004 January 28
    - Distinguished Service Professor Timothy Lance,..., 2002 October 1
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 1
    - Distinguished Librarian Meredith Butler, dean and..., 2002 October 1
    - Distinguished Professor of Social Welfare Jan..., 2002 October 1
    - An unidentified person reviews portraits at an..., 2002 October 1
    - Provost and Vice President for Academic Affairs..., 2002 October 21
    - Minister of Commerce, Industry, and Tourism of the..., 2002 October 21
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 21
    - Susan Palmer, School of Education, pictured with..., 2002 October 22
    - Two unidentified persons stand near a doorway full..., 2002 October 25
    - College of Arts and Sciences Dean Joan Wick-..., 2002 October 25
    - A view of a classroom inside the newly renovated..., 2002 October 25
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 October 25
    - An unidentified person speaks at the dedication..., 2002 October 25
    - Unidentified persons perform onstage at the..., 2002 October 25
    - Bob Fortune of Barry, Bette and LaDuke (BBL..., 2003 October 27
    - Chris D'Elia with an unidentified person at a..., 2002 October 28
    - Executive Advisory Board members Richard Roberts..., 2002 October 28
    - Julie Brokaw of the Bechtel Corporation at the..., 2002 October 29
    - Linda Trocki hands a check to an Billy Stanbery of..., 2002 October 29
    - David Usher, acting chief operating officer at..., 2003 October 29
    - Author William Kennedy and University at Buffalo..., 2003 October 29
    - Author William Kennedy speaks at "The Kennedy..., 2003 October 29
    - Dr. Joan Wick-Pelletier, Dean of the College of..., 2003 October 30
    - University at Albany alumni, Paula Christy-..., 2003 October 30
    - The University at Albany's Kids Growing Food (KGF)..., 2003 October 7
    - The University at Albany's Kids Growing Food (KGF)..., 2003 October 7
    - The University at Albany's Kids Growing Food (KGF)..., 2003 October 7
    - Maggie Mancinelli-Cahill, Producing Artistic..., 2003 November 10
    - Richard Dresser, international playwright and..., 2003 November 10
    - A photo of a painting of University at Albany..., 2003 November 12
    - University at Albany Faculty Michele Przedwiecki..., 2002 November 13
    - From left to right, and unidentified woman and..., 2003 November 14
    - Unidentified students in the auditorium at the..., 2002 November 20
    - Unidentified persons on stage at the taping of..., 2002 November 20
    - Host Chris Matthews preparing for the taping of..., 2002 November 20
    - Host Chris Matthews and Hillary Rodham Clinton at..., 2002 November 20
    - Host Chris Matthews and Hillary Rodham Clinton..., 2002 November 20
    - Host Chris Matthews and Hillary Rodham Clinton..., 2002 November 20
    - University at Albany Professor of English Lydia..., 2003 November 20
    - (From the left) University at Albany Professor of..., 2003 November 20
    - New York State Governor George Pataki shaking..., 2002 November 21
    - Unidentified persons seated in the audience at an..., 2002 November 21
    - William Flynn, chairman of the state Public..., 2003 November 21
    - Two unidentified students of Michael Landin, an..., 2003 November 4
    - Joseph Bowman, Jr., Associate Professor of..., 2003 November 4
    - The 2002-2003 University at Albany men's..., 2002 November 5
    - Susan Phillips, Dean of the School of Education at..., 2003 November 5
    - From left, freshman Aquawasi St. Hillaire and..., 2003 November 6
    - The University at Albany's 2003-2004 Women's..., 2003 November 6
    - An unidentified person working at the opening of..., 2002 November 7
    - Unidentified persons at the opening of Dreidel's..., 2002 November 7
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 December 12
    - New York Senator Charles Schumer speaks at the..., 2002 December 12
    - New York Senator Charles Schumer speaks at the..., 2002 December 12
    - Two unidentified University at Albany students in..., 2003 December 15
    - An unidentified man attends a press conference at..., 2003 December 15
    - Roger Saillant, president and CEO of Plug Power,..., 2003 December 15
    - Helen Adler visits a Humanities Institute for..., 2003 December 3
    - Corporal Andre Williams, class of 2003, presents..., 2003 December 5
    - A group of University at Albany Great Danes' Men's..., 2003 December 5
    - Gil Bindewald of the United State's Department of..., 2004 February 10
    - Jim Fogarty of General Electric attends the Energy..., 2004 February 10
    - Susan Sherman and an unidentified man attend..., 2004 February 11
    - Katharine Briar-Lawson, dean of the School of..., 2004 February 11
    - Individuals attend the University at Albany's..., 2004 February 12
    - Warren Roberts, History professor, and Carlos..., 2004 February 12
    - Hector Mejia, recipient of the University at..., 2002 February 19
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2003 February 24
    - Undergraduate business administration students are..., 2004 February 25
    - University at Albany's Dean of the School of..., 2003 February 28
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 February 6
    - Carl Rosner stands at a podium while University at..., 2002 February 6
    - Carl Rosner converses with Rich Honen. In the..., 2002 February 6
    - An unidentified person, Carl Rosner with his..., 2002 February 6
    - Dr. Alan Sokolow, Frank Negro, Dr. Thomas Auer,..., 2000
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2000
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock,..., 2000
    - The groundbreaking for the University at Albany's..., 2000
    - The second-place runner crosses the finish line in..., 2000
    - Spectators offer encouragement to runners in the..., 2000
    - Another very young runner reaches the finish line..., 2000
    - Peter Casale and Lynda Fleurismond at the..., 2000
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2000
    - Antonia Coello Novello, Commissioner of Health for..., 2000
    - Visitors view exhibits at the Professional..., 2000
    - Deborah Redner (second from L.) receives a..., 2000
    - High school students prepare to compete in the..., 2000
    - Members of the Department of Women's Studies at..., 2000
    - Lee McElroy, University at Albany vice -president..., 2001
    - Carlos Santaigo, Unversity at Albany Provost and..., 2001
    - Musicians rehearse for an orchestral performance..., 2001
    - Musicians watch their conductor for cues during..., 2001
    - Musicians rehearse for an orchestral performance..., 2001
    - Hector Martinez of the Center for Comparative..., 2001
    - Student Jerry Won shares a laugh with Tom Mackey..., 2001
    - Governor George Pataki speaking at the press..., 2001
    - Governor George Pataki speaking at the press..., 2001
    - IBM Vice President speaking at the press..., 2001
    - From left, New York State Senator Jospeh Bruno,..., 2001
    - A student receives guidance through the..., 2001
    - Participants in a Partnership for Literacy seminar..., 2001
    - Professor Gloria Ladson-Billings of the University..., 2001
    - Steven Thomson (L.) of SUNY Albany International..., 2001
    - Kangwon National University President Yong Soo..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock and..., 2001
    - Dignitaries from Kangwon National University and..., 2001
    - Carson Carr (far left) and unidentified guests in..., 2001
    - Congressman and civil rights leader John Lewis..., 2001
    - Professor Grace Mose teaches a class in the..., 2001
    - Colleagues mingle at the 25th anniversary..., 2001
    - Carl Rosner speaks to students at the University..., 2001
    - An honor guard leads the procession at a September..., 2001
    - Leaders of various faiths participate in a..., 2001
    - An unidentified speaker addresses the crowd at a..., 2001
    - The honor guard prepares to lead participants off..., 2001
    - Members of the University at Albany community..., 2001
    - Members of the University at Albany community..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2001
    - An unidentified University at Albany student who..., 2001
    - Students at the University at Albany, New York..., 2001
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002
    - Eliot Sptizer speaks to University at Albany..., 2002
    - Eliot Spitzer addresses the Boosting Business in..., 2002
    - Leonard Slade, Department of Africana Studies..., 2004 March 11
    - Joan Pelletier-Wick, dean of the College of Arts..., 2004 March 11
    - Unidentified persons on the phones during the..., 2002 March 12
    - University at Albany Professor of Physics Carolyn..., 2003 March 12
    - Two unidentified men speak with newly appointed..., 2004 March 12
    - Newly appointed University at Albany interim..., 2004 March 12
    - Hal Lawson, special assistant to University at..., 2002 March 14
    - University at Albany Interim President John Ryan..., 2004 March 17
    - An unidentified person speaks at the podium at a..., 2003 March 19
    - Students and prospective employers attend a career..., 2004 March 2
    - Students and prospective employers attend a career..., 2004 March 2
    - The audience seated outside at a peace vigil for..., 2003 March 24
    - Unidentified persons hold hands at a University at..., 2003 March 24
    - Unidentified high school students tour the..., 2003 March 27
    - Unidentified high school students tour the..., 2003 March 27
    - Ivan Steen (left), Associate Professor Director,..., 2002 March 4
    - Kenneth Jackson during his lecture "The End of..., 2002 March 4
    - Kenneth Jackson during his lecture "The End of..., 2002 March 4
    - William Kennedy addresses the audience at Kenneth..., 2002 March 4
    - An unidentified man shakes hands with William..., 2004 March 4
    - Billy Collins, recipient of the New York State..., 2004 March 4
    - Unidentified persons standing in front of a booth..., 2002 March 6
    - Unidentified persons speaking at a booth for the..., 2002 March 6
    - Unidentified persons speaking at the Army National..., 2002 March 6
    - Unidentified person making a phone call for the..., 2002 April 1
    - Unidentified person making a phone call for the..., 2002 April 1
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 10
    - An unidentified person speaks at the podium while..., 2002 April 10
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 10
    - Towers Perrin management consultant and University..., 2002 April 11
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - MIT professor, physicist, and Noble Prize..., 2002 April 19
    - Members of the University at Albany's "Spread the..., 2004 April 21
    - An unidentified person at an University at Albany..., 2002 April 22
    - An unidentified member of the University at Albany..., 2004 April 28
    - John Ryan, University at Albany interim president,..., 2004 April 28
    - Building plans unveiled at a press conference to..., 2002 April 3
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock,..., 2002 April 3
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 3
    - Assemblyman Jack McEneny speaking at the press..., 2002 April 3
    - Gene Auciello and unidentified persons standing at..., 2002 April 30
    - University at Albany President Karen Hitchcock..., 2002 April 30
    - Alain Kaloyeros, Dean of the School of..., 2002 April 30
    - Panelists discuss ``Tech Valley Today: A View from..., 2002 April 30
    - University at Albany Interim President John Ryan..., 2004 April 30
    - U.S. EPA Administrator Christie Whitman during a..., 2002 April 5